Hello, I'm Adelia Sajida from Bandung.
I have been an FD customer since
[music]
2021.
The reason I remain a loyal
FWD Insurance customer is that FWD provides
convenience and extraordinary service
.  Also, in handling claims that are
not complicated, everything is
made easy.
My FWD story.  Approximately [music]
2 months ago, to be exact, I had
pain in my lower abdomen.
Then go to the nearest hospital.
I was really shocked and didn't
expect that after [music] arrived at the
hospital, after the examination, it turned out that
I had infiltrative appendicitis.
More or less it's appendicitis [music] that
has become swollen.  At
that time I had to be scheduled for the
cooperative the next day without
any preparation.  The next day's action.  But first I asked,
which service do you want,
ma'am?  Do you want VIP or VVP or
the regular one?  I said, "Okay, let's just get
VVP. Because I want to be
comfortable."  That's what it looks like before and after
the operation.  Time passed until
the operation was finally finished.  Then I
spoke to the hospital administration
, "What about the case? Hey, I'm safe.
What about the insurance?"  [music] Okay or
not?  Okay, ma'am.  Everyone is safe.  Well, it
continued until finally after 9 days it was
declared that he would return home on
Sunday.  It was Sunday and I
didn't expect it to be meaningful because on
Sundays all offices are closed,
services are closed, and FWD might even be closed.
But it turns out that's not the case.
I was able to go home before lunch.
I just signed and then I asked,
"How much do we have to pay?"   There are
n't any, ma'am.  Everything [music] is
done.  Take a look at the billing.  Then
I saw the bill with a
certain amount.  I was actually a bit surprised
, [music] a bit surprised because I was a
VVIT with this fee covered everything.
Meanwhile, in my opinion, I myself
only pay ordinary [music] insurance.  So I think the service is
truly extraordinary for its claims.
Then the insurance company itself,
even though it is on holiday, provides the
best service.  Even Eden is
very cooperative.